Guide to the Allegheny Observatory Records, 1850-1977 UA.5.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence of Directors/Acting Directors, 1850-1977; I.
  - Frank Schlesinger, 1899-1920, 1907; 6.
    - Correspondence from AIS/Yale University Project
      - Knopf, Otto (Sternwarte)
      - L.E. Knott Apparatus co.
      - Knowles, Harry (Box 17e, Folder 12)
      - Kobold, Hermann (Astronomische Nichrichten)
      - Kobow, Hermann
      - Koch, S. Marie (St. John's General Hospital)
      - Konkoly, Nicolas (Royal Institute of Meteorology, Budapest, Hungary)
      - Koon, E. (Observatory, Potsdam)
      - Kopf, M.G. (Ralko Products Co.)
      - Kratzer and Co., 1904-1906 (Box 17e, Folder 13)
      - Kratzer and Co., June 1907 (Box 17e, Folder 14)
      - Kratzer and Co., July-December 1907 (Box 17e, Folder 15)
      - Kucera, Otto (Observatory, Zagreb, Croatia) (Box 17e, Folder 16)
      - Kurtz, Langvein and Swartz
      - Kustner, F. (Sternwarte)
      - Laekyn, William (Solar Physics Observatory, London)
      - Lambert, R.C. (Carnegie Steel)
      - Lampland, C.O. (Lowell Observatory)
      - Langley, S.P. (Smithsonian Institute) (Box 17e, Folder 17)
      - Lau, H.E. (Sternwarte)
      - Lauder, George
      - Laves, Kurt
      - Lawrence Paint Store
      - Leavenworth, F.P. (University of Minnesota)
      - Leavitt
      - Lecointe, G. (Royal Observatory of Belgium)
      - Lee, Oliver J. (Yerkes Observatory) (Box 17e, Folder 18)
      - Leete, John B. (Carnegie Technical Schools) (Box 17e, Folder 19)
      - Lefras, Gustave
      - LeGoullon, P.
      - Lehmann-Fillus
      - Leisser, B. (Pittsburgh School of Design)
      - Leland, O.M. (Astronomical Society)
      - Leni, John F.
      - Leon, Luis (Society of Astronomy, Mexico)
      - Leonard, F.C. (Leonard Observatory)
      - Leuchan, H. (Sydney Observatory) (Box 17e, Folder 20)
      - Leuschner, Armin O. (University of California)
      - Lewellyn, C. G. (Box 17e, Folder 21)
      - Libert, Lucien
      - Library Bureau
      - Lick Observatory
      - Liedki, Richard
      - Lincoln, Paul M.
      - Ling, George (Columbia University)
      - Linhart, S.B. (Western University of Pittsburgh - Office of Secretary) (Box 17e, Folder 22)
      - Little, Frank B. (U.S. Naval Observatory) (Box 17e, Folder 23)
      - Lockhart, James
      - Lockwood, W. H. (S.F. Bowser Co.) (Box 17e, Folder 24)
      - Lohse (Observatory Astrophysikalisches, Potsdam)
      - Long, W.F.
      - Longmans, Green and Co.
      - Lord, H.G. (Emerson McMillin Observatory, Ohio State)
      - Lovett, Edgar Odell (Princeton Observatory) (Box 17e, Folder 25)
      - Lowell, Percival (Lowell Observatory, Arizona)
      - Ludendorff (Observatory Astrophysikalisches, Potsdam)
      - Ludwig, W.H.
      - Lumiere N. (America Co., Ltd.) (Box 17e, Folder 26)
      - Lundin, C.A.P. (Alvin Clark and Sons Corp.)
      - Lunt, J.
      - Luterancik, John P. (St. Vincent's Seminary)
      - Lyon, J.L.
      - van Maanen, Adrian (Yerkes Observatory) (Box 17e, Folder 27)
      - MacFarlane, James R. (Carnegie Museum) (Box 17e, Folder 28)
      - MacMillan Co.
      - Maddille, James (International Latitude Observatory)
      - Magill, Endora
      - Magnus, Nyren
      - Magvar Tudomanyos Akadimia (Budapest)
      - Mamaux Sons (Box 17e, Folder 29)
      - Manhattan Electrical Supp.
      - Mann, Ira A.
      - Marcus, Alexander (College of the City of New York)
      - Mars (a poem) (Box 17e, Folder 30)
      - Marsh, Charles E. (Atchinson, Topeka,Santa Fe Railway)
      - Marshall Bros.
      - Marshall, R. (U.S. Geological Survey)
      - Marti, C.
      - Glenn L. Martin Co.
      - Martin, H.S. (War Dept)
      - Martin, John F., Rev.
      - Martin, William C. (John A. Brashear Co.)
      - Marwick, E.E., Col. (Box 17e, Folder 31)
      - Marzolo, P.
      - Mason, H.D.
      - Mason, William A. (Philadelphia Board of Education)
      - Maunder, Thomas F. (British Astronomical Association) (Box 17e, Folder 32)
      - Maury, J.W. Draper (Harvard Club of N.Y.)
      - May, Gertrude B.
      - The May Lumber Co.
      - Mazelle (Maritime Observatorium)
      - McAllister (Electric Service Supplies Co.)
      - McAteer, Charles (Harvard Observatory) (Box 17e, Folder 33)
      - McCasland, May
      - Oliver McCLintock Co.
      - McConway, William
      - McCormick, S.B. (Western University of Pennsylvania), 1905-1909 (Box 17f, Folder 1)
      - McCormick, S.B. (Western University of Pennsylvania), 1912 (Box 17f, Folder 2)
      - McCormick, S.B. (Western University of Pennsylvania), 1913-1915 (Box 17f, Folder 3)
      - McCormick, S.B. (Western University of Pennsylvania), 1916-1919 (Box 17f, Folder 4)
      - McCoutrey (Boggs Buhl) (Box 17f, Folder 5)
      - McDiarmid, R.J. (Dept. of Interior)
      - McDowell, J.B. (Box 17f, Folder 6)
      - McDowell (J.A. Brashear Co.), 1905-1911
      - McDowell (J.A. Brashear Co.), 1912-1920 (Box 17f, Folder 7)
      - McGahan (Westinghouse) (Box 17f, Folder 8)
      - McGee, Anita A.
      - McGill, M.A. (U.P. Theological Seminary)
      - McGuiness (American Warming and Ventilating Co.)
      - McKinley, A.E.
      - McKnight, T.H.B. (University of Pittsburgh)
      - McLane, R. (Box 17f, Folder 9)
      - McLean, Maggie
      - McMaster, Jessie
      - McNaugher, John (Pittsburgh Theological Seminary)
      - McNees (Geologic and Topographic Survey)
      - McNish, Thomas
      - McPherson, William D. (The American Astronomer) (Box 17f, Folder 10)
      - McWilliams, S.E.
      - Meals, Emma
      - Mecklin, J.M. (University of Pittsburgh)
      - Mees, C.E.K. (Eastman Kodak), 1914-1915 (Box 17f, Folder 11)
      - Mees, C.E.K. (Eastman Kodak), 1916-1917 (Box 17f, Folder 12)
      - Meese, L.H.
      - Meggers, W.F. (Dept. of Commerce) (Box 17f, Folder 13)
      - Mendenhall, C.E. (National Research Council, Library Bureau) (Box 17f, Folder 14)
      - Meikle, Anna E. (Case School of Applied Medicine)
      - Mellon, Rachel H.
      - Mellor, Lewis L. (Detroit Observatory)
      - Merrill, Paul W. (U.S. Bureau of Standards)
      - Mershon, Ralph
      - Mesta Machine Co.
      - Metcalf, Joel (Winchester Unitarian Society)
      - Meteorological Observatory of the Imperial University
      - Miles, J. Walter (Westinghouse) (Box 17f, Folder 15)
      - Millas, Jose Carlos (National Observatory - Cuba)
      - Miller, G.
      - Miller, G.A. (University of Illinois)
      - Miller, John A. (Swarthnore College), 1906-1912 (Box 17f, Folder 16)
      - Miller, John A. (Swarthnore College), 1913-1914 (Box 17f, Folder 17)
      - Miller, John A. (Swarthnore College), 1915-1916 (Box 17f, Folder 18)
      - Miller, John A. (Swarthnore College), 1917-1919 (Box 17f, Folder 19)
      - Millikan (National Research Council) (Box 17f, Folder 20)
      - The Millionaire
      - Miscellaneous
      - Mitchell, S.A., 1908-1914
      - Mitchell, S.A., 1915 (Box 17f, Folder 21)
      - Mitchell, S.A., 1916-1917 (Box 17f, Folder 22)
      - Mitchell, S.A., 1918-1920 (Box 17f, Folder 23)
      - Mitchell, S.A., 1906 (Box 17f, Folder 24)
      - Mitchel, Walter M. (Haverford College Observatory) (Box 17f, Folder 25)
      - Moeller, Herman (J.M. Gusky Orphanage and Home) (Box 17f, Folder 26)
      - Monk, George S. (Yerkes Observatory)
      - Society of the Observatory of Mont Blanc
      - Montova
      - Moore, H.K.
      - Morning, Ober (Pottstown High School)
      - Morecroft, J. Arnold (Pratt Institute)
      - Morgan, H.R. (U.S. Naval Observatory)
      - Morris, Brown Co.
      - Morrison, George (United Engineering and Foundry Co.)
      - Morschhauser, W.A.
      - Moseley, E.L.
      - Moulton, F.R. (University of Chicago) (Box 17f, Folder 27)
      - Mourashkinsky, Basil (Box 17f, Folder 28)
      - Oscar Muller Co.
      - Murdoch, Kerr Co.
      - Mutte, Henry
      - National Astronomical Observatory (Tacubaya, Mexico)
      - Naegauirala, R.D.
      - Nail, Mary C.
      - National Academy of Sciences
      - National Press Bureau
      - National Radiator Co. (Box 17f, Folder 29)
      - National Research Council
      - Nature Magazine
      - U.S. Naval Observatory
      - Neodymium (Box 17f, Folder 30)
      - Neodymium (Box 17f, Folder 31)
      - Nernst Lamp Co. (Box 17g, Folder 1)
      - Newall, H.F. (Solar Physics Observatory, Cambridge)
      - Newcomb, S.
      - New Era Printing Co., 1907-1908 (Box 17g, Folder 2)
      - New Era Printing Co., 1909 (Box 17g, Folder 3)
      - New Era Printing Co., 1910 (Box 17g, Folder 4)
      - New Era Printing Co., 1915-1917 (Box 17g, Folder 5)
      - New Era Printing Co., 1919-1920 (Box 17g, Folder 6)
      - New Hampshire State Library (Box 17g, Folder 7)
      - New York Public Library
      - Observatory of Nice
      - Nicholson Printing co.
      - Nicola, F.T. (Schenley Farms Co.)
      - Norris
      - Northwestern University
      - Nutting, P.G. (Westinghouse)
      - Nyland, A.A. (Observatory of Utrecht)
      - Observatory Committee (Box 17g, Folder 8)
      - Olcott
      - Oliver, George F. (U.S. Senate)
      - Olivier (University of Virginia)
      - One Hundred
      - Optical Instrument Monthly
      - Otis Elevator Co.
      - Ott, F.L. (Box 17g, Folder 9)
      - The Pacific Express Co.
      - Paddock, G.F. (Mills Observatory Expedition)
      - Painter, George E.
      - Palmer, Charles
      - Palmer, Harry M.
      - Palmer, Margaretta
      - Pi Co-op (Parallax Committee) (Box 17g, Folder 10-14)
      - Park, J.A. (Box 17g, Folder 15)
      - Park, J.L. (Western University of Pennsylvania)
      - Parker, M.H. (Dept. of Interior)
      - Parker, F.H. (Dept. of Interior)
      - Parkhurst, Henry (Superior Court) (Box 17g, Folder 16)
      - Parkhurst, J.A. (Yerkes Observatory)
      - Pastorelli and Rapkin, Ltd. (Box 17g, Folder 17)
      - Patterson, W.H. (Westinghouse)
      - Paulson, W.S.
      - Payne, William W. (Goodsell Observatory of Carleton College)
      - Pearl, Raymond (National Research Council)
      - Peck, Henry A. (Syracuse University) (Box 17g, Folder 18)
      - Peyram, George B. (Columbia University)
      - Peifer, Charles J. (J.A. Brashear Co.)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad Co.
      - Pennywitt, Henry (Dept. of Agriculture)
      - Perrine, C. (Astronomical Observatory - Argentina) (Box 17g, Folder 19)
      - Pessler, A. (Box 17g, Folder 20)
      - Peters
      - Petersen, Max (University of Wisconsin)
      - Pfund, A.H. (Johns Hopkins University)
      - Phillips, Fracis (University of Pittsburgh) (Box 17g, Folder 21)
      - Phillips, Theodore
      - Photographic Astronomy
      - Pickering, E. (1900-1911,1912-1917) (Harvard College Observatory) (Box 17g, Folder 22-30)
      - Pickering, W. (Harvard College Observatory)
      - Pickering, W. (Harvard College Observatory) (Box 17g, Folder 31)
      - Pierpont, James
      - Pellou, J.L. (Dept. of Public Works)
      - Pillsbury, J.L. (National Geographic Society)
      - Pitman (Swarthmore College) (Box 17g, Folder 32)
      - Pittsburgh and Allegheny Telephone Co.
      - Pittsburgh Calcium Light and Film Co.
      - Pittsburgh Electrical and Machine Works
      - Pittsburgh Fire Extinguisher Co.
      - Pittsburgh Heating Co.
      - Pittsburgh Iron and Wire Works
      - Pittsburgh Map
      - Pittsburgh Printing Co.
      - Plaskett, J.S. (Dominion Observatory, Victoria, South Carolina), 1907-1910 (Box 17g, Folder 33)
      - Plaskett, J.S. (Dominion Observatory, Victoria, South Carolina), 1911-1912 (Box 17g, Folder 34)
      - Plaskett, J.S. (Dominion Observatory, Victoria, South Carolina), 1913-1914 (Box 17g, Folder 35)
      - Plaskett, J.S. (Dominion Observatory, Victoria, South Carolina), 1915-1917 (Box 17h, Folder 1)
      - Plaskett, J.S. (Dominion Observatory, Victoria, South Carolina), 1919 (Box 17h, Folder 2)
      - Plassman, J. (Box 17h, Folder 3)
      - Pluvinel
      - Polar Trails
      - Poole, D. Lewis (Royal Societies Club)
      - Poor, Charles (New York Academy of Sciences)
      - Poor, John (Shattuck Observatory)
      - Popular Astronomy
      - Porter, Edwin K. (City Deposit Bank) (Box 17h, Folder 4)
      - Porter, H.B. (The Scientific Shop)
      - Porter, H.K.
      - Porter, Jermaine G. (Cincinnati Observatory)
      - Postal Telegraph Cable Co.
      - Post Master
      - Pratt, W.H.
      - Price, P.W. (County Engineers Office) (Box 17h, Folder 5)
      - Priest, Mame S. (U.S. Bureau of Standards)
      - Presho, C. (Caton Technical Schools)
      - Pritchett (Carnegie Foundation)
      - Professors
      - Proof (Box 17h, Folder 6-7)
      - Purdy, Ross (Box 17h, Folder 8)
      - Quimby, Alden
      - Le Radium (Physics Journal)
      - Ralko Products Co.
      - Rambaut, Arthur A. (Radcliffe Observatory)
      - Ramsey, Charles N. (Equitable Life Assurance Society of the U.S.)
      - Rasner and Dinger Co. (Box 17h, Folder 9)
      - Rayburn and Bates
      - Raynaud, Michel
      - Rea, James H.
      - Director (Real Observatory)
      - Red Cross
      - Redden, J.M. (Box 17h, Folder 10)
      - Reed and Witting - Stationers
      - Reich, M. (General Engineering and Contracting Co.)
      - Reiche, Louise
      - Reid, A.M.
      - Reimer, George (Verlagsbuchhandlung)
      - Reiss, R. (Box 17h, Folder 11)
      - Remsen, Ira (Johns Hopkins University)
      - Reports
      - National Research Council (Box 17h, Folder 12)
      - Ricco, A. (Royal Observatory of Catania) (Box 17h, Folder 13)
      - Rich, J. and G.
      - Ridgeway, Frank (U.S. Dept. of Agriculture)
      - Riefler, Clemens (Weather Bureau) (Box 17h, Folder 14-15)
      - Rifenburg, F.C. (Phila. Typewriter Supply Co.) (Box 17h, Folder 16)
      - Riggenbach, Albert (Astronomisch - Meterorlogische Anstalt)
      - Rines, David (Coast and Geodetic Survey)
      - Ristenpart, F. (Astrological Observatory Casilla) (Box 17h, Folder 17)
      - Ritchey, G.W. (Solar Observatory, Mt. Wilson, CA)
      - Ritter and Flebbe
      - Robertson, David (Pittsburgh Golf Club)
      - Rockwell, W.W.
      - Roddi, Auguste
      - Roe, E.D. (Syracuse University)
      - Romeiki Inc.
      - Rosedale Foundry and Machine Co.
      - Ross, Frank (International Geodetic Assoc.), 1907-1909 (Box 17h, Folder 18)
      - Ross, Frank (International Geodetic Assoc.), 1910 (Box 17h, Folder 19)
      - Ross, Frank (International Geodetic Assoc.), 1911-1913 (Box 17h, Folder 20)
      - Rowland, K. (Western University of Pennsylvania) (Box 17h, Folder 21)
      - Royal Typewriter Co.
      - Royal Astronomical Society, London
      - Royal Observatory, London
      - Rumrill, H.B. (Pennsylvania Railroad)
      - Russell,Henry Norris (Princeton) (Box 17h, Folder 22)
      - Russell,Henry Norris (Princeton), 1911 (Box 17h, Folder 23)
      - Russell,Henry Norris (Princeton), 1912 (Box 17h, Folder 24)
      - Russell,Henry Norris (Princeton), 1913 (Box 17h, Folder 25)
      - Russell,Henry Norris (Princeton), 1914 (Box 17h, Folder 26)
      - Rust, Frances (Box 17h, Folder 27)
      - Sabisee, Wallace (War Dept.)
      - Sanford, Fernando (Stanford University)
      - Sayer, Luella (Dearborn Observatory)
      - Saylor, E.B. (Western Union Telegraph Co.)
      - Scaife, Lucien
      - Scandrett, Thomas (Dept. of Public Safety) (Box 17h, Folder 28)
      - Schapper, H.
      - Scheiner, J.
      - Schiaparelli, Giovanni (Observatory of Brera-Milan)
      - Schimmack, P.K.
      - Schlesinger, Frank (Publications list)
      - Schoenberg, E.
      - Schoenlein, O.G. (Emmanuel Lutheran Church)
      - Scholer, Eva
      - Schoer, Richard (Sternwarte - Hamburg)
      - Schott Genossen - Jena, Germany (Box 17h, Folder 29)
      - Schoyer, A.M. (Pennsylvania Lines)
      - Schrocter, F.H. (Christiana Observatory - Norway)
      - Schumacher, Elsa
      - Schuster, Arthur (Manchester, England) (Box 17h, Folder 30)
      - Schwab, J.C. (Yale University Library)
      - Schwarzchild, R. (Astrophysikalisches Observatory)
      - Schwob, Adolphe, Inc. (Box 17h, Folder 31)
      - The Science Press
      - Scientific American Compiling Dept.
      - Scientific Materials Co.
      - Scott, Charles (Westinghouse)
      - Seares, F.H. (Solar Observatory)
      - Seckendorff, M.G.
      - Secretary's Office (University of Pittsburgh), 1910-1914 (Box 17h, Folder 32)
      - Secretary's Office (University of Pittsburgh), 1915-1919 (Box 17h, Folder 33)
      - See, F.J.J. (Naval Observatory) (Box 17h, Folder 34)
      - Seed, Dry Plate Co. (Box 17h, Folder 35)
      - Seelinger, H. (Sternwarte - Munchen)
      - Seibel, George (Pittsburgh Gazette)
      - Shapley, Harlow (University Observatory - Princeton
      - Sharman, George H. (Box 17h, Folder 36)
      - Shattuck (8th International Geographic Congress)
      - Shinjo, Shinto
      - Sidgreuves, Walter (Stonyhurst College)
      - Sies, R.F. (School of Education, University of Pittsburgh)
      - Simmons, Guy (Independent Agency, Bureau of Statistics)
      - Simpson
      - Singer, G. Harton
      - Slipher, V.M. (Lowell Observatory, Flagstaff, Arizona) (Box 17i, Folder 1)
      - Slocum, Frederick (Yerkes), 1909-1914 (Box 17i, Folder 2)
      - Slocum, Frederick (Yerkes), 1915-1919 (Box 17i, Folder 3)
      - Smalley, R.E. (Box 17i, Folder 4)
      - Smiley, Charles (Allegheny Post Office)
      - Smith, A.G.
      - Smith, Charles (Fire Insurance)
      - Smith Edwin (Dept. of Commerce and Labor, Coase Geodetic Survey)
      - Smith, Elliott (Cincinnati Observatory)
      - Smith, J.M.
      - Smith, Mason F. (Yale University)
      - Smith, S.B. (Prism Glass Co.)
      - Smith, Walter
      - Smithsonian Institution (Box 17i, Folder 5)
      - Snow, Benjamin W. (University of Wisconsin) (Box 17i, Folder 6)
      - Snyder, Antes (Pennsylvania Railroad)
      - Snyder, M.B. (Philadelphia Observatory)
      - La Societe Imperiale des Naturalistes de Moscow
      - Solar Rotation (Box 17i, Folder 7)
      - Solyom, Herbert (Yerkes Observatory)
      - Somers, Fitler and Todd Co.
      - Southall, James P.C. (Alabama Polytechnic Institute)
      - Spencer Lens Co. (Box 17i, Folder 8)
      - Spieth, William Spindler and Hoyer
      - Springer
      - Spurgeon, John J. (Public Ledger)
      - Standard Roller Bearing Co.
      - Standards-U.S. Bureau of (Box 17i, Folder 9)
      - Stauernagel, Oscar (Box 17i, Folder 10)
      - Stebbins, Joel (University of Illinois)
      - Stechert, G.E. Co. (Box 17i, Folder 11)
      - Stellar Parallax
      - Stellar Spectra
      - Hamburger Sternwarte (Box 17i, Folder 12)
      - Stetson, H.F. (Yerkes)
      - B.F. Stevens and Brown - Trafalgar Square
      - Stevens, Robert L. (Trinity Rectory)
      - Stevenson, Edward A.
      - Stevenson and Foster Co., Pittsburgh
      - Stewart, De Lisle (Box 17i, Folder 13)
      - Stewart Douglas (Carnegie Museum)
      - Stewart, Marie
      - Stewart R. (Western University)
      - Stewart R. Mildrum (Dominion Observatory)
      - Stocker, Florence J. (Radcliffe College)
      - Stockhausen and Sons
      - Stone, Ormond (University of Virginia) (Box 17i, Folder 14)
      - Stratton, F.J. M. (Solar Physics Observatory - Cambridge University)
      - Straub, Max V.
      - Stroingren (Observatory Copenhagen) (Box 17i, Folder 15)
      - Stroobant, P. (Royal Observatory of Belgium)
      - Struve, D.H. (Sternwarte Konigliche)
      - Staub, John
      - John Stulen and Sons
      - Stupakoff, S.H. (Box 17i, Folder 16)
      - Supplee, C.W.
      - Sutton, Psyche Rebecca (The Daily Reporter)
      - Swope, E.F. (William Mitchell Printing Co.)
      - Switchboard
      - System, Fitting Co.
      - Tacchini, Pietro
      - Taggart and Yerxa
      - Tallock, John (Wall Street) (Box 17i, Folder 17)
      - Taylor (University of Cincinnati)
      - Taylor and Dean (Pittsburgh Iron and Wire Works)
      - Taylor, James (Vassar)
      - Tebbcott, John (Observatory-Wales)
      - Technical World Magazine
      - Teller, Sidney (Irene Kaufmann Settlement)
      - Templeton, Alex
      - Terschoffel, A. (Institute of France)
      - Tetens, Otto
      - Thaw, Benjamin (Box 17i, Folder 18)
      - Thaw, H.K.
      - Thaw, Stephen Dows (Box 17i, Folder 19-22)
      - Thiersky, G.W. (Carnegie Institute of Technology) (Box 17i, Folder 23)
      - Thomson, Andrew
      - A.F. Thompson and Co., Boston, MA
      - Thompson, Henry S. (Harvard)
      - Thompson, Mary
      - Thompson, Mrs. William R.
      - Thurston Prep School (Box 17i, Folder 24)
      - Tickel (University of Pittsburgh)
      - Tillyer, Edgar D. (U.S. Bureau of Standards)
      - Times
      - Tittmann, O.H. (Coast and Geodetic Survey) (Box 17i, Folder 25)
      - Todd, D. (Amherst College Observatory) (Box 17i, Folder 26)
      - Todd, James (Sterling Varnish Co.), 1911 (Box 17i, Folder 27)
      - Todd, James (Sterling Varnish Co.), 1912 (Box 17i, Folder 28)
      - Todd, James (Sterling Varnish Co.), 1913 (Box 17i, Folder 29)
      - Tombo, Rudolf, Jr. (Alumni Council of Columbia University) (Box 17i, Folder 30)
      - Toulouse, Univ. de
      - Townley, Sidney D. (Stanford University)
      - Tozer, R.S. (Box 17i, Folder 31)
      - Tracht (University of Chicago)
      - Trinks, W. (Carnegie Technical School)
      - Trubner, Karl J.
      - Truman, O.H. (University of Iowa)
      - Trumpler, R. (Box 17i, Folder 32)
      - Tucker, R. H. (Lick Observatory) (Box 17i, Folder 33)
      - Turk, J.C. (A. S. Wilson Co.)
      - Turner, Arthur B. (college of the City of New York)
      - Turner, Flora
      - Turner, H.H. (University Observatory - Oxford, England)
      - Tyler (Ensign Manufacturing Co.) (Box 17i, Folder 34)
      - Tyson (University of Pittsburgh)
      - Ukiah Observatory
      - Ullman, B.L. (University of Pittsburgh)
      - Union (International Astronomical Union) (Box 17i, Folder 35)
      - Union National Bank (Box 17j, Folder 1)
      - Union Observatory (Johannesburg)
      - United Presbyterian
      - United Press Service
      - United States Express Co.
      - University of Chicago (Library)
      - University of Chicago Press
      - University of Michigan (Library)
      - University of Pittsburgh (Box 17j, Folder 2)
      - University Professors, American Assn. Of (Box 17j, Folder 3)
      - Updegraff, Milton (U.S. Naval Observatory)
      - Vahlen (Preussische Akademie)
      - Valente, John
      - Vallot, J. (Observatory of Mont Blanc)
      - Van Bresbroeck G. (Yerkes)
      - Very, Frank (Westwood Astrophysical Observatory)
      - Vockrodt
      - Voigtlander and Son (Optical Works)
      - Voss Sortiment (Box 17j, Folder 4)
      - Voorhees, Oscar
      - Voute, J. (Royal Observatory)
      - Wadsworth
      - Walcott, C.D. (Smithsonian)
      - Wales Visible Adding and Listing Machine
      - Walker, A. (U.S. Naval Observatory)
      - Walker, C.H. (Editor of Ion) (Box 17j, Folder 5)
      - Walker, Gilbert F. (Indian Observatory - Calcutta)
      - Walker, H.L. (Dollar Savings Bank)
      - Walkey, O.R.
      - Wallace, Daniel H.
      - Wallace, Isabel (Box 17j, Folder 6)
      - Wallace, John Wallace, R. James (Yerkes)
      - Wallin, Sven
      - Walter, G.
      - Waltham Watch Co.
      - War Dept.
      - War Dept. (Office of Chief Signal Officer)
      - Ware, Louise (Yerkes) (Box 17j, Folder 7-11)
      - Warner and Swasey Co. (Box 17j, Folder 12-14)
      - Weimck (Box 17j, Folder 15)
      - Welch, Willia Y. (Clarion State Normal School)
      - Weld, Le Roy (Coe College)
      - Wells Fargo and Co.
      - Wendell, O.C. (Harvard College Observatory)
      - Wenley, R.M. (University of Michigan)
      - West, Andrew (Princeton)
      - West, Laura
      - Western Union Telegraph
      - Westinghouse, Church, Kerr and Co.
      - Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. (Box 17j, Folder 16-19)
      - Westinghouse Machine Co. (Box 17j, Folder 20)
      - Wehterbee, Weston
      - Wettach, James
      - White, Arthur